Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Paper Production Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Frontline: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas
    - Magazine Research: Impacto #2388, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 38)
    - Magazine Research: Impacto #2367, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 39)
    - Magazine Research: Huellas #127, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 40)
    - Magazine Research: Huellas #126, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 41)
    - Magazine Research: Quehacer Politico #742, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 42)
    - Magazine Research: Quehacer Politico #701, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 43)
    - Magazine Research: El Chahuistle #39, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 44)
    - Magazine Research: El Chahuistle #29, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 45)
    - Magazine Research: El Chahuistle #26, 2/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 46)
    - Magazine Research: Como #512, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 47)
    - Magazine Research: Como #476, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 48)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #999, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 49)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #997, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 50)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #996, 12/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 51)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #995, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 52)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #994, 11/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 53)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #980, 8/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 54)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #976, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 55)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #975, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 56)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #974, 7/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 57)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #973, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 58)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #972, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 59)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #970, 6/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 60)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #968, 5/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 61)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #967, 5/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 62)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #965, 5/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 63)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #961, 4/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 64)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #960, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 65)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #959, 3/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 66)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #950, 1/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 67)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #948, 1/1995; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 68)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #934, 9/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 69)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #929, 8/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 70)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #871, 7/1993; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 71)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #528, 12/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 72)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #513, 9/1986; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 73)
    - Magazine Research: Proceso #379, 2/1984; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 74)
    - Magazine Research: Newsweek, 3/1994; 1.0 Items (Carton 77, Folder 75)
  - Corpus: A Home Movie for Selena
    - Diaries: Ms. Portillo's Notebook, 1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 1)
    - Introduction ¯ Project Description, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 2)
    - Lourdes Portillo ¯ Biography/Filmography, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 3)
    - Cineasta Chicana ¯ Reflexiones De Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 4)
    - About The Director, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for The Arts (NEH) Grant, 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 6)
    - Brief Project Description & Budget ¯ Rockefeller Foundation Grant, 1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 7)
    - National Video Resources ¯ Technical Assistance Awards, 2004; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 8)
    - Grant Request: "Ms. Louise Gund", 9/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 9)
    - Grant: Zellerbach Fund Request, 11/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 10)
    - San Antonio Fund Raiser, San Antonio, Texas, 8/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 11)
    - San Antonio Fund Raising Party With Ms. Sandra Cisneros, 8/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 12)
    - Corpus Donation Letter, 7/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 13)
    - Corpus Funders, 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 14)
    - "Thank You" Letter To: National Video Resources, 6/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 15)
    - Music Rights, 1998¯1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 16)
    - Sandra Cisneros ¯ Literary Rights, 7/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 17)
    - Monaco Lab Proposal for Film Work, 9/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 18)
    - Avid Rental Agreement with Chill Productions, 4/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 19)
    - Budget, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 20)
    - Production Invoices, 8/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 21)
    - Buenos Aires, Argentina, 8/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 22)
    - FYI Direct: Brochure Mailing, 12/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 23)
    - Editing Bill ¯ P.O.V., 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 24)
    - NBC News Archives Bill, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 25)
    - Hotels ¯ Venice, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 26)
    - Research, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 27)
    - La Jornada ¯ Mexico, D.F., 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 28)
    - Cineaste Vol. VIII, No. 3, 1977¯1978; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 29)
    - Photography Books, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 30)
    - Actress, Blu River ¯ Santa Fe, New Mexico, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 31)
    - Q Productions ¯ Selena Fashion Catalogue, 1996; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 32)
    - Music Catalogue, 1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 44, Folder 33)
    - Ms. Portillo's Wall Calendar, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 2)
    - Production Calendar, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 3)
    - Production Calendar, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 4)
    - Script, 1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 5)
    - Quintanilla Family Transcript ¯ Abe, Susette, Franco, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 6)
    - Final Corpus Transcript, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 7)
    - Music: Final Cue Sheet With Notes, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 8)
    - PBS Music Cue Sheets, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 9)
    - Music, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 10)
    - Requests For Stock Footage #1, 12/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 11)
    - Requests For Stock Footage #2, 12/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 12)
    - Selena Stock Footage ¯ Sent To Vivian Hillgrove, Editor, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 13)
    - Selena Archival Log: Tapes, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 14)
    - Cinematographer, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 15)
    - Texas Shoot: Contact Sheet & Itinerary Notes, 7/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 16)
    - Texas Shoot: Itinerary, 7/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 17)
    - Itinerary: Buenos Aires, Argentina; Venezia, Italy, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 18)
    - Narration, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 19)
    - Paper Cut Assembly, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 20)
    - Rough Cut Assembly, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 21)
    - Audio Transfer Report ¯ Skywalker Sound, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 22)
    - Skywalker Sound Invoice, 12/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 23)
    - "The Poet & The Pervert" By Cherrie Moraga Re: Yolanda Saldivar (Selena's Killer), 6/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 24)
    - English Subtitles, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 25)
    - Spanish Subtitles, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 26)
    - Spanish Subtitles, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 27)
    - Editing, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 28)
    - Story Boarding Cards, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 29)
    - Dr. Rosalinda Fregoso's Tapes #4, #5, #6, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 30)
    - Handwritten Time Logs Of: Slides, Footage Of Film, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 31)
    - Production Comments By Ms. Portillo ¯ (2 Pgs.), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 32)
    - Notes On Shoots: Handwritten By Ms. Portillo (11 Pgs.), 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 33)
    - Shooting Notes (6 Pgs.), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 34)
    - "Cuts" From Lourdes (L Typed Page), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 35)
    - Production: Shooting Notes (L/2" Thick), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 36)
    - Handwritten Production Notes (1" Thick), 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence with Abraham (Fax), 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 39)
    - Conversations with Abraham Re. Production Problems, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 40)
    - Show Log ¯ Final Cue Sheet for P.O.V. ¯ Photos, Footages, Video Clips, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 41)
    - Credits, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 42)
    - Credits & Scripts, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 43)
    - Rosa Linda Fregoso, Ph.D., 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 44)
    - NPC Productions ¯ In Motion Magazine, San Diego, 11/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 45)
    - P.O.V. Responses/Talking Back, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence with P.O.V., 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 47)
    - Professional Correspondence ¯ Ardeche Images, France, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence: Taos Talking Pictures ¯ Taos Pueblo Libraries, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 49)
    - Interview: Lourdes & Abraham (Selena's Dad) & Greg Nava), 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 50)
    - Lourdes, Abraham & Hector, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 51)
    - Professional Correspondence ¯ Miscellaneous, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence ¯ Spanish, 10/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 53)
    - E¯Mails, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 54)
    - E¯Mails, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 55)
    - Complimentary Letter ¯ Nancy Pelosi, Member Of Congress, 12/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 56)
    - L.A. Free Waves Contribution, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 57)
    - Solo Productions ¯ San Francisco Cinema, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 58)
    - Press Packet ¯ Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 59)
    - Corpus Press Packet, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 60)
    - Corpus: Publicity, Spanish and English, 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 61)
    - P.O.V. Press Clips (Various Cities, States, Countries), 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 62)
    - P.O.V. Viewer Mail, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 63)
    - P.O.V., 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 64)
    - Corpus (From P.O.V.) Reviews, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 65)
    - Press: P.O.V. Reviews, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 66)
    - Various San Diego Clips ¯ 6th Annual San Diego Latino Film Festival, 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 67)
    - Select Press Reviews ¯ English, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 68)
    - San Antonio Scene News Clips, San Antonio, Texas, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 69)
    - La Nacion ¯ Buenos Aires, Argentina, 8/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 70)
    - Excelsior, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 71)
    - Madrid ¯ "Selena...Victima de la Ambicion de su Padre", 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 72)
    - Casa de America, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 73)
    - La Opinion, L.A., 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 74)
    - La Opinion, L.A., 6/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 75)
    - Diario de Tervel ¯ "Los Latinos Debemos...", 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 76)
    - El Mundo, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 77)
    - La Jornada/El Heraldo de Mexico/ Reforma Excelsior, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 78)
    - El Dia "Retrospectiva De Cine Chicano", 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 45, Folder 79)
    - Written Interview of Lourdes Portillo by Catalina Reyes ¯ Taos, New Mexico, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 1)
    - Lourdes Portillo Interview with Rosa Linda Fregoso, Chicago, Illinois, 11/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 2)
    - Lourdes Portillo Interview with KPBS ¯ "These Days" ¯ San Diego, Ca, 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 2)
    - Lourdes Portillo Interview by Vilma Maldonado, The Monitor, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 3)
    - Interview: Ms. Portillo, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 5)
    - Lourdes Portillo Interview Bby Fred Salas, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 6)
    - Interview: "Is Brown Beautiful?" By V. Maldonado, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 7)
    - KBHK ¯ TV Interview with Ms. Portillo, 1/2000; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 8)
    - Lourdes Portillo Interview with Latino USA ¯ National Public Radio ¯ Reyes Entertainment, L.A., Ca, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 9)
    - Abraham Quintanella: Interview Questions (Selena's Dad), nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 10)
    - Chris Perez (Selena's Husband) ¯ People Magazine Interview, 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 11)
    - Notes/Clips On Films Of Lourdes Portillo, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 12)
    - San Diego Latino Film Festival "Smashing Icon", 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 13)
    - San Diego Latino Film Festival: "Corpus" Bidi Bidi Boom Boom ¯ English, 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 14)
    - Corpus Christi Caller Times, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 15)
    - El Sol De San Diego, 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 16)
    - Gay & Lesbian Times, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 17)
    - Gay & Lesbian Times, San Diego ¯ "A Conversation wth...", 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 18)
    - Latina Magazine: P.O.V. "Our Lives Made Public", 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 19)
    - L.A. Weekly, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 20)
    - The Monitor, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 21)
    - The Monthly ¯ Critic's Choice, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 22)
    - San Antonio Express News, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 23)
    - San Antonio Express News, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 24)
    - San Antonio Express News, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 25)
    - Austin American Statesman ¯ "Film on Selena Pulled From Festival", nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 26)
    - San Antonio Current, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 27)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian "Daddy's Girl", 3/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 28)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian "The Heart Of Tejas", 3/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 29)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian ¯ Film Fest, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 30)
    - San Francisco Bay Guardian ¯ "Messing With Texas", 8/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 31)
    - San Francisco Chronicle ¯ Datebook, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 32)
    - San Francisco Gate, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 33)
    - San Francisco Weekly, 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 34)
    - San Francisco Weekly, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 35)
    - Sidewalk San Francisco ¯ Critics' Picks, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 36)
    - San Jose Mercury News, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 37)
    - The Times: Berkeley, CA, 11/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 38)
    - TV Guide, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 39)
    - Weekender, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 40)
    - News Clips Various: Mexico, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 41)
    - Corpus Reviews ¯ Various, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 42)
    - Press Statements Re. Project, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 43)
    - Photographs, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 44)
    - Selena Gift Bag & "Selena The Movie March 21" Button, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 45)
    - People Weekly Tribute ¯ Commemorative Issue, 1995; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 46)
    - Cine Argentino Hacia El 2000 Instituto Nacional De Cine y Artes Audiovisuales, 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 47)
    - Cinema D'oggi ¯ Rome, Italy, 8/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 48)
    - Fabula Magazine, San Francisco, Ca, 12/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 49)
    - ILA ¯ German Magazine, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 50)
    - Venezia News, Venice, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 51)
    - Biennale ¯ Venice, Italy, 12/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 52)
    - Biennale Di Venezia, Venice, Italy, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 53)
    - 56 Mostra Internazionale D'arte Cinematografica, Venice, Italy, 1/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 54)
    - Buenos Aires Film Festival, Argentina, S.A., 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 55)
    - Casa De America: "Madrid Retro", Madrid, Spain, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 56)
    - Exhibit ¯ Sala Iberia, Spain, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 57)
    - Festival Cine Accion ¯ San Francisco ¯ Berkeley, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 58)
    - 22nd Annual Cine Festival, Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, San Antonio, Texas, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 59)
    - Cinema Santa Fe, New Mexico, 12/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 60)
    - Cineteca Nacional, Mexico City ¯ Lourdes Portillo Retrospective, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 61)
    - 40th Festival Dei Popoli, Florence, Italy, 11/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 62)
    - Films Des Femmes ¯ Creteil Film Festival, 11/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 63)
    - Filmoteca Espanola: FIAF ¯ Madrid, Spain, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 64)
    - The Eighth Florida Film Festival, Orlando, Florida, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 65)
    - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, San Antonio, Texas, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 66)
    - 3rd Latino Film Festival ¯ Marin, Ca, 11/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 67)
    - Mexico City Retro, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 68)
    - 6AMostra Latino ¯ Americana Do Rio De Janeiro, Brazil ¯ Cinesul (Includes Poster), 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 69)
    - 4A Muestra Euroamericana De Video Y Arte Digital, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 8/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 70)
    - Nations, Pollinations & Dislocations Film & Video Symposium & Festival ¯ Vancouver, B.C., Canada, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 71)
    - New York International Children's Film Festival ¯New York, New York, 2/2000; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 72)
    - New Zealand Film Festival, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 73)
    - The Other America Film Festival, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 74)
    - San Antonio Film Festival, Texas, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 75)
    - Rockefeller & Macarthur Film/Video/Multimedia Fellowship, New York ¯ Frames Of Reference, 11/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 76)
    - San Diego Latino Film Festival, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 77)
    - 42nd San Francisco International Film Festival, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 78)
    - Santa Barbara International Film Festival, 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 79)
    - Sor Juana Festival: A Tribute To Mexican Women, Chicago, Illinois, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 80)
    - Taos Talking Picture Festival, Taos, New Mexico (3 Files), 3/1999; 3.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 81¯83)
    - Thessaloniki Documentary Festival, Athens, Greece ¯Festival, 4/2000; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 84)
    - 18th Vancouver International Film Festival, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 85)
    - Walker Art Center ¯ Women With Vision 2000 Festival Minnespolis, Mn, 3/2000; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 86)
    - 28 Wellington Film Festival, New Zealand, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 87)
    - "Selena Festival" Worcester, Mass. Edu., Mass., 10/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 88)
    - Yerba Buena Center For The Arts, San Francisco, Ca, 2/2000; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 89)
    - Screening ¯ Antioch Documentary Institute, Yellow Springs, Arkansas, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 90)
    - Screening: Berkeley Art Museum, Pacific Film Archive, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 91)
    - Chabot College Screening, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 92)
    - Guggenheim Museum Screening ¯ Berta Sichel, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 93)
    - Macla Announcement, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 94)
    - Mexican Fine Arts Museum, Chicago, 11/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 95)
    - Mexican Fine Arts Center Museum ¯ Independent Contractor Agreement ¯ Chicago, Illinois, 11/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 96)
    - Multicultural Center Theater, Chicago, Illinois, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 97)
    - P.O.V. Film Festival, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 98)
    - P.O.V. Season 12, New York, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 99)
    - P.O.V. Airing, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 100)
    - Santa Fe Film Festival ¯ Screening Cassette, 10/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 101)
    - Spencer Museum Of Art, Kansas City, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 102)
    - University Of Kansas, 5/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 103)
    - University Of Texas At Austin, Screening Request, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 104)
    - Women Of Color Cluster Screening, U.C., Santa Cruz, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 105)
    - Distribution, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 106)
    - Distribution Notice, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 107)
    - Ardeche Images Production, France, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 108)
    - Monarch Films, Inc., Jersey City, New Jersey, 7/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 109)
    - Alpert Award, Cal Arts, Valencia, Ca, 1999; 2.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 110, 111)
    - Universidad Nacional Autonoma De Mexico, 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 112)
    - Cineaste Award ¯ 1999 Tributee: Lourdes Portillo, 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 113)
    - Cineasta Award ¯ Taos Talking Pictures Festival, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 114)
    - Ida: 15th Annual Awards Competition, Los Angeles, Ca, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 115)
    - Frames Of Reference By Rockefeller & Macarthur, nd; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 116)
    - Universidad De Buenos Aires, Argentina: Lecture, 7/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 117)
    - "Hijas Del Quinto Sol" ¯ San Antonio, Texas, 7/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 118)
    - University Of Texas At El Paso, 8/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 119)
    - University Of Kansas, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 120)
    - University Of California, Santa Barbara, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 121)
    - UC Santa Barbara, 4/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 122)
    - San Francisco State University, 9/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 123)
    - Ancestral Films ¯ Houston, Texas, 6/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 124)
    - Worcester State College, Massachusetts, 10/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 125)
    - Professor Lourdes Portillo ¯ Latinas in Film Class, U.C. Berkeley, 1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 46, Folder 126)
    - Proposal: N.E.A. Proposal, 8/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 1)
    - Proposal: The Rockefeller Foundation, Film/Video/Multimedia Fellowships, 1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 2)
    - Proposal: NBC News Archives: License Agreement, 9/1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 3)
    - Proposal: IRS ¯ Non¯Profit, 7/1997; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 4)
    - Proposal: PBS: Music Rights Outline, 3/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 5)
    - Proposal: P.O.V. Corpus Contract, 2/1999; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 6)
    - Proposal: Music Rights ¯ The Harry Fox Agency, Inc., 1998; 1.0 Folders (Carton 47, Folder 7)